I'm
not in bed. I'm at the rehab center clearing my
head. They brought me here to Blacksburg to
start the fight again. I'm hooked up to a monitor
to watch the pain. The nurses watch me as I move.
I'm walking on the track. My chest is tight, my
breath is short, but I'm coming back. This is the
first day of the rest of my new life. I'm pushing
past the limit. I'm ready to begin. This is the
breaking point. I'm in the recovery zone. I'm
going all the way. I'm not afraid to stand alone.
I'm one in a million. I'm never giving in. This is
the fight. And I'm gonna win.
My sternum's held by wires. I move so slow and
small. I'm hugging on a hot pillow, afraid that I
might fall. But every step is victory A no to her
machine I'm taking back my body I'm wiping the
slate clean The old me is fading, I'm letting him
go A fire's in my heart And it's starting to grow
I'm pushing past the limit I'm ready to begin
This is the breaking point I'm in the red
concrete zone. I'm going all the way. I'm not
afraid to stand alone. I'm one in a million. I'm
never giving in. This is the fight. And I'm going
to win. No more running No more hiding I'm
finally deciding To be the hero of my own story
This
is the breaking point I'm in the recovery zone
I'm going all the way. I'm not afraid to stand
alone. I'm one in a million. I'm never giving in.
This is the fight. And I'm going to win.